[{
    "question": "Statement using 'and' operator results true if: ",
    "a": "Either of the operands is true",
    "b": "Both operands are false",
    "c": "Both operands are true",
    "d": "First operand is true",
    "answer": "c"
},
{
    "question": "Who created python?",
    "a": "None of these",
    "b": "Guido van Rossum",
    "c": "Mark Zuckerberg",
    "d": "Aliens",
    "answer": "b"
},
{
    "question": "What is the lastest version of python?",
    "a": "4",
    "b": "9",
    "c": "2",
    "d": "3",
    "answer": "d"
},
{
    "question": "Where is creator of python from?",
    "a": "USA",
    "b": "Mars",
    "c": "Netherland",
    "d": "Poland",
    "answer": "c"
},
{
    "question": "What sites from these are written in python?",
    "a": "YouTube",
    "b": "All of these",
    "c": "Google",
    "d": "Reddit",
    "answer": "b"
},
{
    "question": "Which of these is exponent operator?",
    "a": "**",
    "b": "/",
    "c": "*",
    "d": "%",
    "answer": "a"
},
{
    "question": "What is n variable there? n = '5'",
    "a": "String",
    "b": "Integer",
    "c": "Float",
    "d": "Tuple",
    "answer": "a"
},
{
    "question": "?",
    "a": "",
    "b": "",
    "c": "",
    "d": "True",
    "answer": "d"
},
{
    "question": "?",
    "a": "True",
    "b": "",
    "c": "",
    "d": "",
    "answer": "a"
},
{
    "question": "?",
    "a": "",
    "b": "True",
    "c": "",
    "d": "",
    "answer": "b"
}]
